<Document>
    # Welcome!
    Hello and welcome to Weasel Station! We have a focus on fun and have rules to match, you may be saying to yourself "I dont want to read these, why do I have to follow rules to have fun?"

    ## TL;DR
    There’s a lot here, but the gist of the rules is roleplay takes priority. Don’t murder just for fun if you’re not antag. Don’t metagame. Don’t play to win. Don’t be a jerk OOCly. If you don’t understand what those words mean or you need more detail, read on!

    # Main Rules: Read if nothing else.

  - [textlink="0. Enforcement of these rules is at the discretion of admins, and therefore interpretation is up to them." link="RuleWS0"]
  - [textlink="1. Don't be a dick." link="RuleWS1"]
  - [textlink="2. Don't discriminate against others." link="RuleWS2"]
  - [textlink="3. Generally, no sexual content/themes, including erotic roleplay (ERP)." link="RuleWS3"]
  - [textlink="4. Regularly coming close to breaking rules will be treated as if rules have been broken." link="RuleWS4"]
  - [textlink="5. Players must be and act at least 16 years old." link="RuleWS5"]
  - [textlink="6. Do not exploit/multikey nor attempt to evade bans." link="RuleWS6"]
  - [textlink="7. Speak English, please." link="RuleWS7"]
  - [textlink="8. Do not use information gained outside of in-character means and vice versa." link="RuleWS8"]
  - [textlink="9. Do not abuse, ignore, or threaten to use the 'Ahelp' system." link="RuleWS9"]

  ## Roleplay Rules
  These rules only apply during a round, a round ends when the round summary has appeared. All of these rules apply fully until the moment that the round summary appears. The deathmatch and sandbox game modes are exempt from these rules.

  Roleplay rules do not apply to ghosts/spectators/observers while they are ghosts/spectators/observers. Dead chat is considered to be an in-game out of character chat channel.

  See the list of [textlink="role types" link="RoleTypes"] for more information about the different types of roles.

  - [textlink="1. Certain roles are held to unique standards, if you play them expect to be held to them." link="RuleWSRP1"]
  - [textlink="2. Roleplay as a semi-normal person." link="RuleWSRP2"]
  - [textlink="3. Escalate conflicts with caution and reason." link="RuleWSRP3"]
  - [textlink="4. Don't act like an antagonist unless the game tells you that you are one" link="RuleWSRP4"]
  - [textlink="5. Don't interfere with arrivals or stall the round." link="RuleWSRP5"]
  - [textlink="6. As an antagonist, do not damage the round beyond your objectives nor undermine yourself or team." link="RuleWSRP6"]
  - [textlink="7. Stick to your role." link="RuleWSRP7"]
  - [textlink="8. Use a reasonable character name." link="RuleWSRP8"]
  - [textlink="9. Do not powergame." link="RuleWSRP9"]

  ## Policies
  As discussed in [textlink="Roleplay Rule 1" link="RuleWSRP1"], we have certain policies that pertain to certain roles. You do not have to read these unless you intend to play one of these roles.

  - [textlink="Silicon Policy" link="WeaselstationSiliconPolicy"]
</Document>